( SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING )
( PLAYING TUNE )
WOMAN : Curl your fingers .
Curve .
( PLAYING NOTE )
( SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES )
( MUSIC FADES )
( CLOCK TICKING )
( SOFT SCRAPE )
( SOFT RATTLE ) ( PUFFS )
( MUFFLED KNOCKING )
( LIGHT KNOCKING )
( CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING )
( LOUD SCRAPE ) ( GASPS )
( BREATHING RAPIDLY )
( SOFT THUD )
( CLATTERING )
( UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING )
( MUSIC HALTS )
( THUD )
( SWING CREAKING )
( DOOR THUDDING ) ( WIND BLOWS )
( DOOR CREAKS )
( UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING )
( FLOOR CREAKS SOFTLY )
( MUFFLED KNOCK )
( MUFFLED KNOCKING ) ( GASPS )
( DOOR OPENS )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( GASPS )
Peter ?
I heard something .
What ?
Peter ?
What time is it ?
What did you hear ?
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES )
Come on .
This one ?
Hmm .
I don 't hear anything .
Do you ?
This is an old house .
There 's bound to be bumps in the night .
( SIGHS ) Come to bed .
( SIGHS )
You have a great , big , beautiful imagination .
And all those scary things ?
( SOFTLY ) They 're just in your head .
( LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING )
( STUDENTS CHATTERING )
( GRUNTS )
BOY : ( LAUGHS ) You 'll get more at recess .
( NOISY SHOUTING )
All right , settle . Settle .
( SHUSHING )
Students .
This is Miss Devine .
She 'll be your substitute teacher
until Mrs. Bitler comes back .
Good luck .
MISS DEVINE : Good morning .
As your principal just said , my name is Miss Devine .
I look forward to getting to know each and every one of you .
( WHISPERING ) Peter .
Recess is coming .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGS )
Okay ...
Oh !
Hi . Um ...
Peter .
( SIGHS ) You 're supposed to be at recess .
I don 't like recess .
You don 't want to play with your friends ?
Okay . You can stay here .
Yeah , you can help me with the decorations .
I love Halloween .
Do you know what you 're going as ?
Well , you have plenty of time to figure it out .
( PETER GASPING )
Look , it 's okay . It 's okay .
It 's okay . Here .
Um ...
Yeah , and take this and slide it under , okay ?
It 's okay .
( SHUDDERS ) Yeah .
There you go . Like that .
Pick it up . We 're gonna take this to the window .
( STUDENTS PLAYING )
Um ...
What am I gonna be for Halloween ?
I want to dress up . I want to trick-or-treat .
All the other kids at school get to do it .
And we 're not their parents .
( SMACKS LIPS )
Hey , Pete . ( CLEARS THROAT )
You know the old house down the end of the lane ,
with the boarded windows ?
He 's going to find out eventually .
( WHISPERS ) Carol . PETER : What ?
Well , a few years ago , before you were born ,
the little girl that lived there ,
she vanished on Halloween .
PETER : What happened ?
MARK : Well , nobody knows .
She went out trick-or-treating and she disappeared .
( CAROL SHUDDERS )
It was a very traumatic event .
For everybody in the neighborhood .
And I , personally ,
don 't like remembering it .
Am I gonna disappear ? CAROL : Oh , Peter .
Of course not , honey . No .
We would never let that happen to you . Ever .
Okay ?
( SLOW SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES )
( ALARMING MUSIC PLAYING )
( MUFFLED RUSTLING )
( MUFFLED RATTLING )
YOUNG GIRL : ( WHISPERS ) Peter . Daddy !
YOUNG GIRL : No , Peter . Don 't tell him .
Daddy ! ( FOOTSTEPS APPROACH )
Peter .
( PANTING ) Pete ?
What 's going on ?
I heard something again .
( SIGHS ) Peter .
( TEARFULLY ) I really did , though .
All right , and , uh , from where ?
( SHUDDERS )
Okay .
( SIGHS )
You know what ? I bet it 's rats .
But I 've got something that 'll take care of that .
Rats ?
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
It smells like cinnamon .
Well , be careful .
Not everything is as sweet as it seems .
PETER : They eat it ?
MARK : That 's the idea . Then what ?
Well ...
( IMITATES THROAT-SLIT )
( CHUCKLES )
Pete , we can 't have rats .
They bite . They ... They spread disease .
Not to mention , keep you up all hours of the night .
Mm-hmm ?
I guess .
( SIGHS ) Look .
( SIGHS )
Sometimes , you have to make tough decisions
to protect your family .
You understand ?
Mm-hmm .
( POPS LIPS )
MISS DEVINE : " Throws his shadow on the floor .
" And my soul from out that shadow
" that lies floating on the floor ,
" shall be lifted ...
" nevermore . "
( GRIM MUSIC PLAYING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( BIRD CAWING )
( DOORBELL RINGS )
( DOOR UNLOCKS )
( DOOR OPENS )
May I help you ?
Uh , are you Peter 's mom ?
Yes ...
( HESITANTLY ) Sorry for showing up like this , uninvited .
I 'm Peter 's teacher .
Substitute .
Of course , he did mention that he had a substitute .
Never known one to make house calls .
Yeah , I just wanted to come over
and ... and check on him personally .
Hmm . I was a teacher myself .
That was before I ... I became a mother .
Is he all right ?
Peter ? Yes .
Um ... ( CHUCKLES )
I ... I did want to show you something .
What 's this ?
The children were drawing for Halloween .
Peter painted this ?
Yes . Yes .
The other children drew monsters and witches , but Peter ...
I see .
Huh . Well , this is embarrassing .
You see , Peter has an overactive imagination .
( TUTS )
He still wakes his father and I up
in the middle of the night
with all of his little flights of fancy which , uh ,
which is all this picture is .
I do appreciate your concern though .
( DOOR OPENS )
( DOOR LOCKING )
What is this ?
A drawing . A drawing of what ?
A drawing of what ?
This is your room , Peter . Why are you asking for help ?
I 'm not .
Why are you asking strangers for help , Peter ?
( FIRMLY ) I 'm not .
( SOFTLY ) She is . What was that ?
It 's just a scary drawing , Mom .
Oh , that imagination of yours , Peter .
It 's going to get you into trouble one day .
( UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING )
( MUFFLED KNOCK )
THE GIRL : ( WHISPERING ) Wake up , Peter .
( LOUD KNOCKING )
Peter .
Don 't be scared .
I just want to talk .
PETER : Please be quiet .
I 'm imagining you .
You 're not real .
THE GIRL : Maybe , maybe not .
But it seems to me like you could use a friend .
I know I could .
But if you don 't want one , I 'll just leave .
( MUFFLED FOOTSTEPS )
PETER : Wait , don 't go .
I 'm sorry .
Please stay .
THE GIRL : Are you sure ?
PETER : Yes , we can talk .
MISS DEVINE : Peter , this is great . What 's his name ?
Hector .
Of course .
He looks like a Hector .
( WHISPERING ) This one 's my favorite .
Shh .
( DARK MUSIC PLAYING )
( CHILDREN CHATTERING )
( SCHOOL BELL RINGS )
( SWINGS CREAKING )
( PETER GASPS , GRUNTS )
Stop !
Please !
( MELANCHOLY VOCAL MUSIC PLAYING )
THE GIRL : ( WHISPERING ) Peter . Are you there ?
( CRYING QUIETLY )
Are you okay ?
Why are you crying ?
Did someone hurt you ?
PETER : Mm .
Brian .
He shoves me down every day .
THE GIRL : I was afraid of something like that .
But I believe in you , Peter .
PETER : Mm .
THE GIRL : I bet you 're strong enough to stand up for yourself .
If you just try .
( DARK MUSIC PLAYING )
GIRL : Busted . ( STUDENTS LAUGHING )
I 'm sorry , Peter .
( STUDENTS LAUGHING )
That was very nice of Brian , wasn 't it , Peter ?
THE GIRL : Show him you 're not afraid anymore .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGS )
( ALL CLAMORING )
THE GIRL : Make him afraid of you .
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
You have to push back .
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATION )
( MUSIC BUILDS UP )
BRIAN : Peter ! Why are you ...
( SCUFFLING ) ( BRIAN YELPS )
( THUD ) ( BRIAN SCREAMING )
BOY : Help !
( BRIAN CONTINUES SCREAMING )
CAROL : ( MUFFLED ) I don 't understand how this could have happened !
Peter has never done anything like this before !
He doesn 't have a violent bone in his body !
It was an accident . I 'm sure of it .
MARK : Expelled ?
Do you have anything to say for yourself , Peter ?
Peter ?
I didn 't mean for him to fall down the stairs .
For God 's sakes . We are not a family
that solves our problems with violence , Peter .
Ever .
I don 't understand where this kind of behavior comes from !
Peter drew a picture . For school .
What ? I 'm sorry .
I know that I should have told you earlier .
But I ... Hold on , hold on . What kind of picture ?
What kind of picture , Carol ?
CAROL : A child .
A child asking for help .
What ?
I knew that you would jump to conclusions .
You 're only telling me this now ?
And it 's just not possible . MARK : Okay , stop .
Even when I tell you about ... MARK : Stop .
Peter . Why would you draw a picture like that ?
( BREATHES SHAKILY )
( SHOUTS ) Peter ! Because I really heard her !
No , you did not ! No !
( MARK BREATHES DEEPLY )
You 're grounded .
Okay , Peter . Go to your room .
No , no , no ! Carol , he 's grounded .
He 's going in the basement .
Now .
( CREAKING )
( MARK SIGHS )
( OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING )
Stand up .
I said , stand up .
MARK : Get up .
( EERIE MUSIC PLAYING )
( PETER SHUDDERS )
Go .
Mom ? ( CAROL SIGHING )
Sit .
( WHIMPERS )
We 're doing this because we love you . Because we love you .
( DOOR SLAMS )
( FRIDGE SCRAPING )
( BREATH TREMBLING ) Hello ?
Are you there ?
Please talk to me .
( MELANCHOLY VOCAL MUSIC PLAYING )
( CRYING )
( RATTLING ) What a stupid thing .
God damn it !
Why won 't you work ? PRINCIPAL : You went to a student 's house ?
( SIGHS ) I did .
I wanted to make sure that Peter was okay .
( SAD MUSIC PLAYING )
PRINCIPAL : Is he showing up with bruises ?
No , not that I can see .
Does he wet himself ?
Is he talking about sex or other things a boy his age shouldn 't know about ?
No .
Then , unfortunately , there 's nothing we can do .
There are a lot of Peters .
Delicate little kids you want to protect from life 's cruelties ,
but you can 't get personally invested .
You 'll be eaten alive .
( SIGHS )
You 've met his parents ? His mother , there 's something ...
off about her .
PRINCIPAL : There 's a child that disappeared
from their neighborhood years ago .
( GRUNTS )
Something like that
would make any parent overprotective .
( OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( WASHING MACHINE WHIRRING )
( DOORBELL RINGS )
( KEYS JINGLE )
Hello . Hi .
I have Peter 's last math quiz .
I thought you should have it . He only missed two .
Thank you for coming by .
Uh ... MARK : Hi , there .
Honey , this is Miss Devine .
Peter 's former teacher .
Nice to meet you .
She was just coming by to drop off his last math test .
That 's wonderful . We can hang it on the fridge .
( CHUCKLES DRYLY )
Please , come in .
We just made coffee .
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
MARK : ( MUFFLED ) This way .
( DOOR LOCKING )
Have a seat .
Thanks .
( DRINK POURING )
( STOPS WHIRRING )
Here you go .
MISS DEVINE : You 're bleeding .
Oh , I 'm just doing some remodeling .
Loose nail .
Don 't worry about it . ( CHUCKLES )
Uh , well , since I 'm here ,
I just want to express how sorry I am
about what happened . Aw .
That 's very , very sweet of you .
But honestly , no apology necessary .
Peter is a spirited boy .
Uh , do you have any idea where Peter will be going to school ?
Of course , we do .
Here . At home .
Oh .
Carol is the best teacher Peter could ever have .
What ? You don 't think that 's a good idea ? Uh ...
I just think that , um , ( SMACKS LIPS )
given his behavior , he might benefit from an environment
more suited toward his needs ?
( CHUCKLES ) No , we 're not going to give our son away .
Thank you . No . No .
No . No , we 're not . Family is what he needs .
( MUFFLED ) Family 's what he 's gonna get .
Where is he ?
He 's grounded . In his room .
May I see him ? No , you may not .
I don 't think it 's appropriate .
I would just like to say goodbye .
What is your interest in our son ?
You 're no longer his teacher . So , I ... I don 't ...
It 's very strange to me
that you continue to show up at our house .
I just wanted to make sure he was all right .
I 'm sorry , " that he was all right " ?
You think that Peter 's in danger ?
Do you think that I 'm the kind of mother
that would harm my child ? Okay .
Honey . It 's okay . CAROL : I love Peter .
We love Peter . We love Peter .
With every fiber of our being .
You don 't know anything about ...
Hey . Hey , enough . No . No . Before ...
How dare you ? How dare you come into our home ...
MARK : Honey , honey , honey . Carol . Carol . Stop .
CAROL : ... for you to tell us what 's best for our son .
MARK : She doesn 't ... Listen to me .
( WHIRRING LOUDLY )
What mother gives up on her child ? Sweetheart , that 's enough .
CAROL : The audacity of this woman ! This stranger .
( KNOCKS )
You don 't know anything . MARK : Don 't let the opinion
of a stranger upset you . ( MUFFLED KNOCKING )
Enough . Hey . Enough .
CAROL : No , before I had Peter , the doctor said
Peter 's a miracle ... Help !
CAROL : ... and I would never give up on him .
I would never give him away . Never . Peter 's a miracle .
An institute , for what ?
Help !
Excuse me . I think you better leave .
I 'm sorry . This was a mistake .
( CONTINUES WHIRRING LOUDLY )
( STOPS WHIRRING ) ( THUDDING )
What is that ?
What ?
The noise . The banging .
The washing machine . ( MACHINE CLICKS )
( WHIRRING )
Please .
( BREATH TREMBLING )
( KNOCKING ) ( GASPS )
Forgot your keys , Miss Devine .
Thanks .
You 're welcome .
( MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING )
( TIMER TICKING )
( TIMER DINGS )
( DOOR OPENS )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
You can come out now .
Here .
Pumpkin .
For our pumpkin .
Well , Peter .
Have you had time to think ?
About what ?
About how I need to grow up .
Stop acting out . Stop telling lies .
And no more nightmares .
No more .
We 're very proud of you , Peter .
Things are going to be different from now on .
You won 't be going back to school any longer .
I 'm gonna be your teacher now . MARK : That 's right .
Your mom here , she 's going to teach you the three R 's , Pete .
You know what they are ?
Readin ' , Writin ' , and Arithmetic . ( LAUGHING )
Oh ...
Okay , I 'm sorry .
You 're a good boy , Peter .
Oh , and we love you .
And we forgive you .
Love you too .
( MELANCHOLY VOCAL MUSIC PLAYING )
CAROL : Goodnight , Peter .
MARK : See you in the morning , son .
Good night .
( DOOR CLOSES )
( FOOTSTEPS LEAVING )
( MUFFLED DOOR CLOSES )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Please talk to me .
( MUFFLED KNOCK )
THE GIRL : ( WHISPERING ) Peter . I was worried about you .
PETER : My mom and dad locked me in the basement .
THE GIRL : I knew it .
You have to be careful with them .
They are not what they seem .
I want to see you . No .
I 've been here too long .
You wouldn 't like the looks of me .
You 'll scream and get us caught .
No , I won 't . I promise .
Okay .
There 's a hole behind the wallpaper .
Do you see it ?
( OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING )
( BALL CLATTERS )
( UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING )
( GASPS )
( BREATHES RAPIDLY )
( NERVOUSLY ) Who are you ?
I 'm your sister .
Hmm ?
I 've been waiting , Peter .
I had to wait till you were big enough .
Big enough for what ?
THE GIRL : Big enough to move the clock that hides the door .
Big enough to help me escape . To leave the dark .
To leave the wall .
( NERVOUSLY ) Please stop . No , you 're scaring me .
THE GIRL : You need to be scared .
Mom and Dad , they 're evil , Peter .
Now you know .
Your time is coming .
( GASPS )
( LOUD KNOCKING )
( CLOCK TICKING )
( SOFT SCRAPING )
Hello ?
( SCRAPING )
Mom ?
( UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING )
( GASPING SOFTLY )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( EERIE MUSIC PLAYING )
Hello ?
Mom ?
Mom ? ( BREATHING RAPIDLY )
MARK : Peter .
( TEETH CHATTERING )
( SPOOKY MUSIC BUILDING UP )
( CHATTERING INTENSIFIES )
Look what you 've done to your mother , Peter .
( MUFFLED RUNNING FOOTSTEPS )
( FOOTSTEPS STOP )
( CLOCK TICKING )
( PETER CRIES OUT )
Peter . ( GASPING )
You were screaming and thrashing around .
Shh .
It 's okay . It was just a bad dream .
Wha ...
What was it about ?
I ...
I don 't remember .
Well , it can 't hurt you now .
PETER : ( WHISPERING ) If they keep you in their room ,
then how are you talking to me ?
THE GIRL : I escaped .
I scratched and clawed my way to you .
Mom and Dad ? They hate me , Peter .
Once they 've had enough of me , I 'm finished .
They 'll kill me .
And they 'll put you in the wall .
No .
They wouldn 't do that .
They wouldn 't kill anybody .
No , Peter .
They already have .
You need to see what 's buried in the garden .
I 'll tell you where .
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( CLACK )
( SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING )
CAROL : Peter .
( INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING )
Peter .
What are you doing ?
( MUSIC QUIETS )
I was thinking that , um ,
I know I can 't go trick-or-treating ,
but maybe we could carve a pumpkin .
THE GIRL : It was Halloween .
Before they locked me in the wall .
( PUMPKIN SQUELCHING )
A trick-or-treater came to the door .
I asked her for help .
( WHIMPERS ) And she saw me .
They killed her , Peter .
( SNIFFLES )
I don 't want to end up like that girl .
I 'm getting you out of there .
I 'm gonna get you out of there and then ,
then we 're gonna run away .
We 're gonna be a family . A real one .
But how ?
PETER : I think I know somebody that can help .
( SIGHING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( KEYPAD BEEPING )
( LINE RINGING )
( MUFFLED CHILDREN CHATTERING )
( CELL PHONE BUZZING )
Hello ?
( WHISPERING ) Miss Devine ?
Peter ?
I need your help .
What did you say ?
( CREAKING )
( GASPS )
( JARRING CHORD PLAYS )
( PHONE RINGING )
Hello ?
Hi , is this Peter 's mom ?
It is . Is this Miss Devine ?
I think Peter just tried to call me .
He did , indeed .
Peter was just telling me how dearly he misses his teacher ,
and so I said , " Peter , just give her a ring .
" Tell her yourself . "
But unfortunately , his shy streak seems to have gotten the best of him .
He 's like a little blushing bride over here .
It 's so cute . ( CHUCKLING )
Well , better luck next time , I suppose .
So sorry to have bothered you . Have a happy Halloween .
( SLAMS RECEIVER )
( UNNERVING MUSIC PLAYING )
That was bad , Peter .
I 'm sorry .
You did a very bad thing .
( GASPS ) You called a stranger ?
She doesn 't know best for you .
She doesn 't love you the way your father and I do .
I am so disappointed in you .
What is that ?
It 's nothing !
( SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING )
( PETER SHUDDERING )
No .
No , no .
No . No .
( BREATHING RAGGEDLY )
No .
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
( WHIMPERS )
What ... What did she tell you ?
( SHOUTS ) What did she tell you ?
( CLOCK TOLLING ) ( GASPS )
It doesn 't matter . Whatever .
( VOICE QUAVERING ) Whatever happens now , it will be your fault .
You just wait until your father gets home .
( SOBBING )
( UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING )
THE GIRL : ( WHISPERING ) Peter .
Peter .
I heard them .
( DOOR CREAKING )
They know .
They are going to kill us .
Peter , you have to do something .
Peter .
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATION )
( UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES )
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATION CONTINUES )
Clean house . That 's all there is to it . I don 't want to .
We can 't keep finding temporary solutions .
That is ... ( OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( MUSIC INTENSIFYING )
( MUSIC QUIETS )
I know you 're awake , son .
You get a good night 's sleep .
When I get home tomorrow , you 'll help me out in the garden .
There 's a problem we need to take care of .
( DOOR CREAKING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( GRIM MUSIC PLAYING )
( INSECTS BUZZING )
MARK : It 's black rot . Killing off the whole garden .
And blight like this ,
it spreads fast .
Get rid of it now or ...
or all the healthy pumpkins will get infected .
And we can 't have that .
We 're going to bury the pumpkins ,
and we 're going to hope that the next crop is better .
Better luck next time .
You understand ?
So , I want you to pick up that shovel
and dig .
( INSECTS CONTINUE BUZZING )
( EERIE MUSIC PLAYING )
Hey , cuz , this is the house ?
Yeah .
Wicked .
( INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING )
Sorry .
( SNIFFLES QUIETLY )
( DOORBELL RINGS )
Can a family not eat in peace ?
( SPOON CLACKS )
( MARK SIGHS )
Stop playing with your food , Peter .
( DOOR OPENS ) CHILDREN : Trick-or-treat !
CAROL : Go away ! ( DOOR SLAMS )
( DOOR LOCKING )
Porch light off ?
Yes .
( SIGHS )
Did you do something different with the soup tonight ?
Did I do something different with the soup ?
MARK : Yeah .
No .
I mean , it 's delicious . It 's great . Right ?
It just tastes a little different .
Hmm .
( SNIFFS )
It smells like ...
( SNIFFING )
Smell it . Yeah , it smells like cinnamon .
Mm .
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( DOOR THUDDING IN DISTANCE )
( DOOR THUDDING )
Peter .
Peter . Have you done something ?
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
Peter .
Son , look at me .
Tell me the truth .
What have you done ?
What did you do ? You tell me .
Tell me , what did you do ?
You hurt my sister .
What did you say ? Oh , my God .
Oh , my God .
( SHUDDERING )
Call 911 .
What is going on ? Call 911 !
( GROANS )
( INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING )
( MARK GROANING LOUDLY ) ( GASPING )
( WHIMPERING )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANS HEAVILY )
( CONTINUES RETCHING )
( SHUDDERING )
Peter !
Stop !
( INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING )
( GRUNTS )
( RETCHING )
( COUGHS )
( GAGGING )
( GRUNTS ) ( SCREAMS )
( BONES CRACK ) ( CLOCK TOLLING )
( UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING )
( SHUDDERING )
Peter . ( SCREAMS )
( WHISPERS ) Don 't let her out .
( GRUNTS )
( PETER PANTING )
( WEAKLY ) Don 't let her ...
out .
( DOOR UNLOCKS )
THE GIRL : ( WHISPERING ) Peter , is that you ?
( CLOCK TICKING )
Did you do it ?
Are they gone ?
I don 't know .
I think so .
THE GIRL : Do you have the keys ?
( KEYS JINGLING )
Yeah .
THE GIRL : The clock .
Be careful .
It 's so heavy .
( GRUNTING )
( GRUNTS )
( CREAKING )
( EERIE MUSIC PLAYING )
Peter . Are you all right ?
( SHUDDERS ) I 'm okay .
Do you see it ?
Do you think you could open it ?
( MUSIC BUILDING UP )
( DOOR UNLOCKS )
( DOOR RATTLES ) ( GASPS )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( HEAVY BREATHING )
( BREATHING GROWING LOUDER )
( GASPS )
( WICKED LAUGHTER )
( UNNERVING MUSIC PLAYING )
( RUSTLING )
( GASPING )
( MUFFLED THUDDING )
( GASPS )
( HEAVY AND RASPY BREATHING )
( IN RASPY MATURE VOICE ) Good boy , Peter .
What was it like watching them die ?
( DOORBELL RINGS ) BOY : Trick-or-treat !
THE GIRL : Just like the girl in the garden .
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
BOY : Hey , Peter ! You alone in there ?
We just came by to say hi .
( MUSIC BUILDING UP )
( DOOR UNLOCKS )
( DOOR CREAKING )
Are they fucking with us ?
Let 's get this done .
( UNNERVING MUSIC PLAYING )
BOY 2 : Hey , Peter .
Are you here ?
( GRUNTS )
( SING-SONGY ) We know you 're in here !
Peter , where the fuck are you ?
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( DOOR OPENS )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( LIQUID DRIPPING )
What the fuck ?
( MUFFLED BANGING )
( PIANO KEYS CLANGING STRIKING )
( STRIKING CONTINUES ) ( OBJECTS CRASHING )
( MUFFLED GRUNT )
( BED SQUEAKING )
( PETER SCREAMING )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANS )
( GRIM MUSIC PLAYING )
( PIANO KEY CLANGS )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
Huh ? ( GRUNTS )
( YELPS ) ( CRUNCH )
( BOY 1 SCREAMS LOUDLY )
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( DRAMATIC SPOOKY MUSIC PLAYING )
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS ) ( DOOR CLACKS )
( GASPS )
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS ) ( GASPS )
BOY 2 : No !
( SCREAMS )
Brian , my leg !
It 's got my leg . Brian , help me !
( BOY 2 SCREAMS )
( BOY 2 GROANS , SCREAMS )
Brian , help me !
No ! No !
( PANTING ) ( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
( GASPS )
( THE GIRL SNICKERING )
( SNICKERING CONTINUES )
( SNICKERING AND FOOTSTEPS STOP )
( BREATHES NERVOUSLY )
( INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING )
( SCREAMS )
( OBJECTS CRASHING )
( BRIAN SCREAMS ) ( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
BRIAN : No , no !
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
( BRIAN CONTINUES SCREAMING )
( SCREAMING CEASES )
BOY 3 : Brian ?
What ?
Brian ?
Brian !
( RUNNING FOOTSTEPS )
( CRUNCHING ) ( BOY 3 SCREAMING )
What did you say ?
( GASPS ) ( TIRES SCREECH )
( PANTING )
Go !
( HARD THUMPING ) ( GASPING )
( OBJECT CRASHES )
( BOY 3 GRUNTING )
BOY 3 : No ! ( GRUNTS )
( FLESH RIPS ) ( THUDDING )
( SHUDDERS )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( BED SQUEAKING )
( CONTINUES IN MATURE VOICE ) When you were born ,
they were so happy .
When I was born ,
they screamed .
So , Daddy made me a pit .
Then he made me a cage .
While you were whining in this warm bed ,
I was suffering among cobwebs and rats ,
learning how to climb .
how to bite ,
learning how to make you do what I want .
Trick-or-treat .
( PETER SCREAMING )
( SNICKERING )
PETER : Let me go , please !
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
PETER : ( SCREAMING ) Help !
You 'll be safe in here .
( BANGING ON DOOR )
( DOORBELL RINGS )
( DOOR CREAKING )
Hello ?
( THE GIRL CRYING )
Peter ?
( BREATH TREMBLING )
Peter .
( SOFTLY ) Oh , my fucking God . What the fuck ?
( DOOR CREAKS ) ( GASPS )
( YELPS )
( WHIMPERING )
( RAPID FOOTSTEPS )
( BREATH TREMBLING )
( SHRIEKS )
( PANTING )
( DOORKNOB RATTLING )
PETER : ( YELLS ) Run !
( BREATH TREMBLING )
Peter ?
PETER : ( YELLS ) Miss Devine ! Peter .
PETER : Miss Devine , run !
( BREATH TREMBLING )
( PETER SCREAMING ) Miss Devine , run !
Miss Devine , run !
Peter ! God . Oh , my God .
You have to run .
No , no , I 'm not leaving you here .
You have to get out of here !
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
( BANGING ON DOOR )
( GASPING )
What the hell is that thing ?
It 's my sister .
( FOOTSTEPS RETREATING RAPIDLY )
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
( DOOR SLAMS ) She 's coming !
MISS DEVINE : Stand back .
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
( GRUNTING )
Peter , come on . Come on , Peter . Come on .
Come on , Peter .
Where are you going ? PETER : The keys .
Come on . Go , go .
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
( PETER SCREAMING )
No ! ( SCREAMING )
( MISS DEVINE YELLS )
( GASPING )
( GASPS )
( SHUDDERING )
Why are you like this ?
( IN MATURE VOICE ) Not every child can be as perfect as you , Peter .
I was just born this way .
And no one loves a monster .
MISS DEVINE : Peter ! Miss Devine !
( BREATH TREMBLING )
MISS DEVINE : I don 't know what you are ,
but if you hurt him ,
I 'll fucking kill you .
( SHRIEKS )
No ! ( GASPING )
( SCURRYING FOOTSTEPS )
Miss Devine !
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GROWLS )
( SHRIEKS )
( GASPING )
( SNARLS )
( GRUNTING )
( SNARLING )
( SCREAMS )
( SNARLING ) ( SCREAMING )
( SCREAMING )
( GRUNTING )
( GROWLING )
( SQUELCHING )
( PETER GRUNTS )
( THUDDING )
( SNARLING )
THE GIRL : ( WHISPERING IN CHILD 'S VOICE ) Peter !
Please .
You 're my brother .
( SHUDDERS ) Peter , let 's go .
THE GIRL : Don 't you see , Peter ?
It 's in our blood .
You killed Mom and Dad .
You 're just like me .
No !
I 'm not like you .
THE GIRL : ( IN MATURE VOICE ) Do you really think this is gonna keep me down here ?
Every night ,
when you lie in bed ,
you 'll wonder if you locked the door ,
or saw a shadow move .
( CREAKING )
Every creak ,
every groan ,
every tap in the wall ,
you 'll think of me .
We 're family , Peter .
I will always be with you .
Always .